Andres Escala

Full Stack Developer



Personal Info

Email

andres.escala@hotmail.com andres.escala.344@gmail.com

Phone

+52 5545464585

Skills

HTML5, CSS3 y Javascript ****

Frameworks: Nodejs, EJS, Reactjs

Git and Github Management

Management of MySQL, SQL Server and MongoDB databases ****

Linux - Ubuntu and CentOS 7 ****

WebApps deployment on Netlify, GitHub Pages, and Azure ****

C#, .Net and ASP .Net Framework



Software

Microsoft Office



Languages

English ★★★★

Full Stack developer and 8th semester telematics engineering student with 2 years experience in web applications and RESTFULL API development in .NET (1 year), Node.js and Express.js (2 years); 6 months experience on Frontend Apps dev with React.js. One year experience in managing SQL Server and MongoDB databases.

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andres-escala-2b98a4222/

GitHub repository: https://github.com/escalandres Portfolio: https://escalandres.github.io/portfolio/

Work History

2022-11 Web Developer Intern

- present Info100 S.A de C.V, Mexico City

Development of a web application for prevention of money laundering with ASP.Net Framework, ASP.Net Razon and SQL Server. And REST API building with .Net 7, and management of CentOS 7 servers

2022-08 Internship Student

- 2022-10 New Ventures, Mexico City

Develop an administration system to store company's social impact programs on ClickUp. And development of a landing page on WordPress for a social impact program's new edition.

2022-03 Student at Bootcamp Web Development

- 2022-05 Innovaccion Virtual, Mexico City

Develop Full Stack web projects with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Nodejs, GitHub and Azure.

2020-01 School projects

- present Instituto Politecnico Nacional, Mexico City

3 years of experience developing apps with C, Python, and web techs like HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Reactjs, Nodejs, Git and Github.

Education

2020-01 Telematics, Bachelor of Telematics Engineering

- present Instituto Politecnico Nacional, Mexico City

Projects

2023-07 *MyYT_Downloader*

- 2023-08 A youtube videos downloader desktop app developed with Node.js,

Express.js Electron.js, HTML5, CSS3 and Bootstrap 5. Available:

https://github.com/escalandres/myyt-downloader

2022-02 ChatAppProject

- 2022-06 School project of a chat application in real time with React.js Node.js. And

deployed on Heroku and Netlify. https://chat-app-project-ing-web.netlify.app/

2021-09 Coffee Pet

- 2021-12 School project of a pet reservation site for a pet friendly cafeteria; developed

in Node.js, EJS, and SQL Server

Certificates

2022-02 Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals